What motivates you to work or study harder?
是什么激励你更努力地工作或学习？
Is it the thought of success and all the amazing things that you can achieve, or is it the fear of failure and worry about all the things that can go wrong for you?
是对成功的憧憬以及你能实现的所有了不起的事情，还是对失败的恐惧以及对所有可能出错的担忧？
Leaders, managers, and teachers have often used one of these ideas to inspire people to work harder and achieve more.
领导者、管理者和教师常常利用这两种想法之一来激励人们更努力工作并取得更多成就。
But is one better than the other?
但其中一种比另一种更好吗？
A recent study looked at the effect of fear-based strategies on British secondary school students.
最近一项研究考察了基于恐惧的策略对英国中学生的效果。
As is so often the case, it's complicated.
和通常一样，情况很复杂。
They found that if a test is seen as important, and students are optimistic that they can succeed, then the fear of failure can be used successfully by teachers to motivate these learners.
他们发现，如果一项测试被视为重要，并且学生对自己能成功感到乐观，那么教师可以成功地利用对失败的恐惧来激励这些学习者。
However, if students are not confident, then fear-based approaches could trigger feelings of anxiety, which can in turn lead them to do worse on the test then they would have done otherwise.
然而，如果学生不够自信，那么基于恐惧的方法可能会激发焦虑情绪，这反而会导致他们在测试中表现得比本来更差。
The study also found that if students are disengaged and don't care about the test in the first place, then, unsurprisingly, the fear of failure is not likely to motivate them.
研究还发现，如果学生原本就不参与、不在乎测试，那么毫不意外，对失败的恐惧不太可能激励他们。
Entrepreneurs often run the risk of failure.
企业家常常面临失败的风险。
It's a fact that most new companies will fail.
事实上，大多数新公司都会失败。
But does this motivate or inhibit businesspeople?
但这会激励还是抑制企业家呢？
Again, it's not straightforward.
同样，答案并不简单。
The personal consequences of failure can be significant, and so founders may be motivated to work harder to avoid them.
个体失败的后果可能很严重，因此创始人可能有动力更努力工作来避免这些后果。
A study carried out on British and Canadian entrepreneurs found that fear of failure can improve problem solving, as people are motivated to anticipate and resolve potential issues.
一项对英国和加拿大企业家进行的研究发现，对失败的恐惧可以改善问题解决能力，因为人们会受到激励去预测和解决潜在问题。
They may also be inspired to learn new things that will help their business or find mentors who can support them.
他们也可能会受到启发，学习有助于他们生意的新知识，或者找到能够支持他们的导师。
However, the study also showed that it can lead to increased procrastination as people focus too much on what they personally fear, rather than what would be best for the business.
然而，研究也表明，这可能导致更加拖延，因为人们过于关注个人恐惧的事情，而不是什么对生意最有利。
If someone is less confident about their business idea, then they may find their decision-making negatively affected by their fears.
如果某人对自己的商业想法不够自信，那么他们可能会发现自己的决策受到恐惧的负面影响。
Taken together, these studies show that fear-based motivation is complicated.
综上所述，这些研究表明，基于恐惧的动机是复杂的。
It can drive confident people to do better, but it can also amplify our doubts and turn them into barriers.
它可以驱使自信的人做得更好，但也可能放大我们的疑虑，并将其变成障碍。